I wanted to say good day to you this day
of your time. How are you all?
All right.
All right. Thank you. Once again, we
thank each and every one of you and all
of you together collectively for the
co-creation of this interaction and the
allowance of this transmission. this day
of your time. We will begin this
transmission
titled You Are All Time Travelers in the
following way. First a brief reminder of
some things we have talked about
regarding what time is.
Time remember
is a side effect. a side effect of your
consciousness shifting
over and over and over and over and over
and over again to different points of
view of the same single moment of
existence
and making it appear to be different
moments.
You can use the analogy we have used
before that these different moments are
themselves parallel realities
that can be illustrated as frames if you
wish on a film strip. So each frame is
its own reality but it has no movement
in it, no experience in it. In a sense
no awareness in it,
no self-reflectivity in it. Each frame
is a single snapshot, a static snapshot
of a potential position,
a potential state of being, so to speak.
Therefore, when you move, when you shift
your perspective, your consciousness
through the different frames one after
another, as you say,
like a projector light through a film
strip, you get the illusion of
continuity, the illusion of movement,
the illusion that creates the experience
of time and space and change and growth
and difference.
Now,
if you will look at the top page of your
handouts
where you see all the different squares,
one group the A group, another group the
B group,
and each has an arrow moving through it
from left to right.
In the A group, you see that all the
squares represent different frames,
different parallel realities that your
consciousness will shift through to
create the illusion of time. You shift
through these parallel realities, these
frames,
billions of times per second, literally
to create that smooth illusion of
physical reality and time and space,
blinking through them so quickly you
don't even realize that you're actually
shifting from one reality to another
that many times per second. But you are.
Now in the top example, the arrow
appears to be going relatively straight
from left to right. This is usually how
your consciousness sort of perceives the
idea as a smooth continuity. One moment
after the next, one progression after
the next, one step after the next in
some sort of logical continuous way or
experience.
Now, it can be in a sense that way. The
frames could line up that way next to
one another. However,
more likely and more often, more
commonly, the picture is actually more
like group B. You're actually jumping
all over the place into different frame
moments as you determine for yourself
what the next experiential frame ought
to be that serves you best for whatever
your belief system has to be or happens
to be at that moment. Therefore, even
though you may actually be jumping
around so to speak. Now again remember
this is an illusion even unto itself
because everything is actually here and
now. All the frames are here and now.
They're not really spread out like this.
This is just the easiest way to simplify
the concept in your three-dimensional
reality fourthdimensional when you
include the concept of time as you move
through the frames so to speak.
But it is more like the idea of skipping
around all over the place. Now, the
point is is you may not actually know
you're doing that because it will still
feel like
group A, like the arrow in group A. It
will still feel like you're just moving
straight ahead, frame after frame,
stepping stone after stepping stone in a
logical continuous progression with none
of this jumping around.
However,
as you start to expand your
consciousness, as your senses become
more aware that you're creating the
illusion of time and space,
you may begin to experience what we will
call breaking continuity. And breaking
continuity can be experienced more often
than not like suddenly things are
happening in a more accel. You don't
necessarily experience what normally
would have been the in between moments.
It's kind of the result of a how did I
get here moment. How did that happen
moment. There wasn't enough time for me
to get to this place, but I got here
anyway moment. Those kinds of slippages
of space and time that allow you to
experience a break in continuity is the
result of your consciousness becoming
more aware of the fact of group B.
you're jumping around all over the place
all the time anyway. So, becoming more
aware of that fact can actually allow
you to perceive that you're jumping
around like that all over the place and
actually create the sensation of a break
in continuity so that time and space
starts skipping around or you start
skipping around within it in ways you
couldn't imagine would be possible
before. You can accelerate things, slow
things down, take detours and perceive
them as you do them.
Now, this is the basic framework that is
happening with regard to what we're
going to discuss about time travel and
how you use this in various ways. So,
you may turn to the second page, if you
will, of your handout.
Looks like a lot more fun there, doesn't
it?
>> Anyone flashing back to their schoolwork
days? Oh, what do I have to memorize
now? You have to memorize nothing. Just
follow along. Whether you understand all
of this, whether it all sinks in right
now or not is not the point. We will
walk you through it. you will absorb
whatever you need to absorb at this
particular moment. But it's really not
that difficult. Understanding again the
basic premise that there are many
different kinds of frame moments,
parallel reality framework moments that
you move through in your own way that
create your sensation of moving through
time and space. So at the top you see
simply the basic layout. The idea that
as you move through life and you go from
being a baby to being a child to being a
teen to being an adult to being a senior
these just represent major frame moments
within the entire spectrum of your life
and the rows below them represent the
same moments in your life. So
the idea is that time travel in the way
that your science fiction stories
portray it is not really the way it
works.
It is all about the idea of shifting to
parallel realities that may be very very
similar to your own. And so you might
not immediately be able to tell the
difference that you actually haven't
traveled in your own timeline, but I'm
telling you that you haven't. And
example number one gives you the perfect
illustration of why that doesn't happen.
If you look at the idea of again the
symbol at the top, you go from the idea
of the baby to the child to the teen to
the adult to the senior. Then look at
the first row of the second example.
example A and you go all right this
person in the top row is a baby and then
they become a child and a teen but as an
adult suddenly they invent time travel
and they decide I'm going to go back and
I'm going to see myself as a child a
younger version of myself
now you would think as most of your
sci-fi stories propose to you that
you're actually going back to your
childhood. You're not in the sense that
you recognize yourself as being an adult
traveling back in time to meet a younger
version of yourself.
That's very different than what you
experienced as a child not having met an
older version of yourself. That frame
when you went through your childhood,
those frames are those frames. And if in
those frames you never met an older
version of yourself coming back and
saying, "Hi, I'm your future self."
Then you can't change those frames.
Those frames are fixed. They are those
frames. The frame that just has you in
it as a child and not your future self.
So when you do then have the experience
of traveling back in time quote unquote
and actually running into your younger
self and introducing yourself as the
future self that's taking place in a
parallel reality where in that reality
that child met you
not even from that child's timeline but
from another parallel timeline. But now
you've become part of that child's
timeline history.
And now that's child two. That's
timeline two. As you can see by the
numbers in that example.
And as you then interact with that child
and that child grows up, that child
still grows up as child two. Now, when
you decide, all right, well, I'm going
to go back to my own time when I left.
You can't do that exactly either because
look at the diagram where it shows that
the adult in the top row has left to go
back to meet the child self in the other
reality. That frame doesn't include you
anymore. It's blank and it always will
be. You can't go back to that moment.
You can't go back to that reality. So
when you decide to get in your time
machine and again quote unquote go back
to the future,
you will find that you will be in a
different parallel reality again.
You will be the senior of that reality
because now you've changed your own
experience of history by meeting your
childlike self which didn't happen in
the primary timeline.
So you're skipping all over the place
becoming another version in a sense
shifting your consciousness to become
another version in another parallel
reality of yourself.
Now look at the next example. the idea
that says actual time travel rather than
parallel reality time travel. If you
actually literally went back in time in
your own timeline, you wouldn't meet
your child's self. You would be your
child self
because your consciousness exists all
the way up and down the timeline
already. So the idea of literally
traveling back in time in your own
timeline means you simply experience
yourself literally as the child again
and are right in that moment where the
child has no idea what it's going to
grow up to be. You are literally that
child and nothing else at that moment.
It's almost like creating a loop where
you're living it over again.
That's what actually would happen in
time travel is you would not know you
had timeraveled. You would simply find
yourself being the child exactly the way
you did experience being the child and
you would have no idea you're going to
grow up and invent a time machine.
It would just be you experiencing
yourself as the child.
Now, at the bottom, you have a similar
idea, but the dotted line means you're
not actually physically traveling back
in time. It's just that you're allowing
your consciousness to in a sense slide
back down the timeline
and experience the idea of the child.
But this is simply what you call a
memory.
That's what memory is. You're actually
allowing your consciousness to slide up
and down the timeline, but only your
consciousness. And you are experiencing
the idea of remembering what it was like
to be the child in that moment and sort
of reliving that experience, but you're
not actually committing fully to having
timeraveled down your timeline to be the
child. You are simply allowing yourself
to continue to remember that you are the
adult having this experience of
remembering that childhood moment. You
are time traveling in your timeline but
only with your consciousness, not with
your physical self. And that kind of
time traveling you call a memory.
Doing that kind of time traveling in the
opposite direction in what you call the
future is what you call the idea of
being psychic and predicting the future
in a sense. Again, there are still the
engagement of all the different parallel
realities so on and so forth. There's
all these probabilities. You don't
necessarily know which one will be the
absolute one that you will experience.
But nevertheless, you can perhaps be
sensitive enough to figure out the
probabilities of what might happen and
maybe move in that direction as you keep
shifting through these parallel frames
of existence.
Is this making some sense so far?
>> All right. If you do have questions or
require clarifications about any of
this, certainly you may do so if you
have been called up for questions a
little bit later. But right now this is
the fundamental idea and the fundamental
understanding that lays the foundation
for the concept that we are discussing
this day of your time. Now
how do you start navigating these frames
in a more conscious way to your
advantage? How do you become an expert
time traveler?
This always goes back to the formula
that we've given you. Now that you have
a better understanding or at the very
least a diagram that your brain can
relate to, now that it can actually see
some form of layout, some presentation
of how this works and it can relate to
those images. The idea of acting on your
passion to the best you can with no
insistence or assumption as to what the
outcome is supposed to look like is
actually your navigation tool. It will
automatically
guide you through the frames that are
most representative of the path of least
resistance, the path through these
frames that is actually best for you. Go
back to page one.
Look at diagram B
where the arrow seems to be jumping all
over the place on its route through
those frames. Now,
as you
really start aligning more with your
passion, following that formula,
allowing the tools in the kit of
excitement to work to your advantage,
and choosing to remain in a positive
state, no matter what happens,
responding to it in a positive way so
that you can get the benefit from it, no
matter how it looks.
that will start to determine exactly
what that path looks like. And every
single time, every single time you make
any alteration whatsoever in the belief
systems within you, even the slightest
alteration, the slightest change, that
arrow that is jumping all over the
place, will completely change its form
and you will be skipping through it in a
different path. The next change,
skipping through it in a different path.
The next change, skipping through it in
a different path all the way through.
Why? Because, as we have told you, every
single change you make actually changes
your past as well as your future. You're
always in the present. So, it's not like
you're going to go, "All right, well,
the path starts out here, then goes
there, then goes there, then goes there.
Well, I'm going to make a change here,
and so it might be different from that
point forward." No, it will also be
different from that point backward
because as you become a different person
from the linear framework point of view,
you have to have you have to create a
different history that brought you to
the point of being the person you say
you are now. That's how it works in
physical reality. You have to have the
continuity of having the past that works
to make you the person you say you are
in the present. Making sense?
>> So the entire arrow, the entire path
changes.
So the idea is again you can navigate
this more consciously.
You can start experiencing
more breaks in continuity,
experiencing more flexibility,
malleability, plasticity in space and
time. Things can start happening much
more synchronistically,
much more magically.
When you allow yourself to truly align
more strongly with your passion, act on
it, to ground it, to commit to it
through your physical action, that
demonstrates the energy that creates the
energy that radiates the frequency that
acts as your rudder through these
frames, through these parallel
realities.
And that will continue to determine
exactly what path you are taking. So
that you will always only then be
experiencing the frames that are always
to your best benefit, to your advantage,
always representative of the path of
least resistance, always representative
of the path of connection to all things
that are relevant to you in your life.
Always giving you exactly what you need,
supporting you in that way, and always
allowing you the freedom to choose to be
who you prefer to be. That's how it
works. Does this make some sense to you?
>> All right.
So, let all of this just sort of simmer.
Let it all sink in. The handout is yours
to ponder at any time. You may have
other insights that may come up just by
the planting of this seed. But please
understand, you are all already time
travelers. This is your nature. You're
not learning to do something you don't
already do. This is for the purpose of
helping you to become aware, more aware,
more conscious of what you're already
doing so that you can utilize it to your
advantage in a more conscious way. So
that you can begin to truly expand your
senses and become more sensitive to the
changes that take place in your
experience of reality and learn to
recognize when major shifts are actually
occurring that are breaking your
continuity so that you can leap for joy
at the quantum leap you have just made.
In a sense it can actually feel like not
that you're doing this literally but can
actually feel like you are skipping over
frames.
So the idea then is you will feel
accelerated.
You will feel again that there is very
little resistance. Your challenges will
all be exciting and expanding.
You will grow from them and you will be
living the birthright that you deserve
to live. So use this tool to your
advantage. It is a powerful recognition
to understand how reality works. When
you can truly see the structure of
existence and understand that you can
use it to your advantage this way, many
things will become very clear and many
questions that you may have had will be
easy for you to answer.
>> Yes.
So we thank you for allowing us to share
this tidbit of timely information
and we ask now in what way may we
continue to be of service to you. Please
begin your questions and dialogues if
you wish.
Good evening.